（和）よッ
（和）よいしょっと　ハア…
Here we go.
（和）うん？
（和）これって…
Isn't this...
Dear Sokabe-senpai.
〈（和）拝啓　曽我部先輩　初夏の候
いかがお過ごしでしょうか→〉
How is your summer going?
〈今日は　先輩にお知らせしたい
ことがあり　手紙を書きました〉
I'm writing today because I have something to tell you.
・～
Shoot! We can't stop! We won't stop!
Singing out loud all day long!
We'll all take the chance to
jump up and make a wish,
and shout out
about our fun lives!
If we mess up, let's pretend it's a rehearsal and redo it!
Everyone has their own little cosmos which we call "heart."
It's tightly packed with emotions and love.
We're busy getting excited, blue, or in-between.
It's chaos every day, so might as well make a song out of it!
And sing all about it!
We unconsciously study music even in class.
We can start making rhythms with air guitars!
It's the feeling that counts!
Imagining the beats, we'll enjoy ourselves freely!
You lose if you can't have fun!
Sorry! We can't let go! We won't let that go!
Swinging around in every possible way like crazy girls,
we'll hit whatever note we want to!
Maybe groove a little like that, and reverb like so.
We want to try everything, until we die.
We'll chase tomorrow together,
dream a little when we take a break.
Let's be bold and faithful and shake this stage up a bit!
Once you feel the ovation, you can't get enough of it!
Visit www.coalguys.com for hi-speed DDLs!
Mio-chan?
（唯）澪ちゃん？
（澪）えッ？
What's wrong? You look scared.
どうしたの　そわそわして
いや…　何か今日は
Well, it feels like someone's been watching me the entire day.
朝からずっと視線を感じるんだ
（紬）澪ちゃん　人気者だから
Well, you're popular.
いや　そんなんじゃなくて…
No, it isn't like that.
まるで　誰かに
監視されてるような…
It's like someone's stalking me.
（律・唯・紬）じ～ッ
Hey, stop!
（澪）見るなッ
You're being way too self-conscious.
（律）自意識過剰なんじゃないの？
ホントなんだって→
I'm serious!
今も何か　どこからか
こっちを見てるような視線を…
Even now, it feels like someone's watching me.
Guess who?
（さわ子）だ～れだッ→
あれッ？
Huh?
（唯・律）さ～わ～ちゃん…
（さわ子）えッ？
Sawa-chan...
Tea Party!
・（さわ子）ふ～ん　誰かの
視線を感じる　ねえ…
You feel like someone's watching you?
Well, it happens to me all the time.
まッ　私はいっつも
見られまくってるけどね
Yeah, since you kinda look pretty.
さわちゃん　外見はいいからな～
'Kinda'? What do you mean?!
「は」って何よ　「は」って
Don't tell me you're the stalker?
澪を追っかけてる犯人って
さわちゃんじゃないの？
Oh, please!
や～ね～　私だったら
見るだけじゃすまないわよ
If it were me, I'd be in jail already.
Yeah, you're right.
ですよね～
アハハハハハ
わかった　犯人はトンちゃんだ
えッ？
I've got it!
It's Ton-chan.
Well, you're afraid of Ton-chan and you don't play with him enough, so she...
ほら　澪ちゃん　トンちゃんのこと
怖がって　あんまり
かまってあげてないから
トンちゃん
貼りついちゃったんだよッ
stuck to your back!
Stop! Stop! It's scary!
（澪）怖い　怖い　怖いッ
It's hopeless.
〈（澪）駄目だ　この人達じゃ
頼りにならない…〉
These guys aren't any help at all.
Hey, I think you should all take this seriously!
（梓）ちょっと！　皆さん　もっと
まじめに心配してあげてください
There really could be a stalker!
ストーカーに
狙われてるかもしれないんですよ
梓…
なるほど…
Azusa...
I see.
謎は全て解けました　犯人は…
The mystery is solved.
The culprit is...
Y-You!
あ　あなたですッ！
（紬）ごめんなさい
一度やってみたかったの
I'm sorry, I wanted to try that once.
But I wasn't kidding about solving the mystery.
でも　謎が
解けたっていうのはホント→
Mio-chan, you ate yakisoba bread this morning, didn't you?
澪ちゃん　今日の朝ご飯は
焼きそばパンだったんじゃない？
Y-Yeah, I slept in this morning, so I bought breakfast on the way here.
えッ　た　確かに…
今朝は寝坊して→
朝ご飯をゆっくり食べてる
時間が　なかったから…
And I bet it was 20% off.
その焼きそばパン
２０％引きだったでしょ
How could you possibly know that?
な　何でそこまでわかるんだ！？
（紬）フフフフッ
ほら　これ
うん？→
Look at this.
ああッ！
I see!
なるほど　一日中
それを髪にくっつけてたのね
You had that on your hair all day.
So that's why everyone was watching me...
それで　みんな見てたのか…
What are you girls doing? Peeking?
・（和）あなた達
何のぞいてるの？
（１年生Ａ・Ｂ）うわッ
（澪）和　この子達は？
それが…
Nodoka, who are they?
Well...
Wait, we're by no means anyone suspicious.
（Ａ）別に
怪しい者ではありませんッ
We are members of your fanclub!
（Ｂ）私達は
澪先輩ファンクラブの者です
Fanclub?
ファンクラブ…
I was trying to forget about that...
（澪）そのことは　もう
忘れようとしていたのに…
Did you come here to see the sticker on her hair?
もしかして　澪ちゃんの髪に
シールがついているのを見に？
Yes! The other members told us about it.
はいッ　他の会員から聞いて
If you're fans, then why didn't you tell her about it?
ファンなら　どうして
すぐに教えてあげないの？
私は教えた方が
いいって言ったんですけど
I said we should, but...
でも　そういうのつけてるところが
先輩らしくて素敵なんです！
But we find it fabulously amazing
since it brings out her character!
You do?
私は　わざと
つけてるのかな～って思ってたよ
Well, I thought you were doing it on purpose.
お前は知ってたのかッ
You knew about it?!
ごめん　私が
しっかりしてなかったせいで…
Sorry, it's my fault I got
careless about the fangirls.
Why are you apologizing?
何で和が謝るんだ？
ファンクラブって　まだあったんだね
But you know, I didn't know the fanclub's still around.
Yeah.
（紬）ね～　曽我部先輩が卒業して
なくなっちゃったんだと思ってた
I thought it got disbanded after Sokabe-senpai graduated.
Who's Sokabe-senpai?
曽我部先輩って誰ですか？
あれ　梓は知らないんだっけ？
Oh, you don't know, Azusa?
Sokabe-senpai was the president of the Mio Fanclub.
曽我部先輩は　澪ちゃんの
ファンクラブ　会長だった人だよ
Yeah.
そうか…　あれからもう
そんなに長い月日が流れたか
Who would have known it's
been so long since that day...
That day?
あれから？
そう　あれは卒業式前の３月
Yes, it was March a little before graduation.
あの日も澪が　誰かに見られてる
気がするって怖がってたから…
Mio was trembling about a stalker like today, and...
《（澪）ううッ…》
見かねた私が
生徒会に相談してみればって
I couldn't stand seeing her like that, so I told her she should go talk to the student council.
アドバイスしたんだ
そうだったんですか
妄想もたいがいに　しとけよ
Really?
Don't get too carried away with your delusions.
誰もまじめに
心配してくれなかったから
No one took me seriously, so I went to the student council myself.
自分で生徒会室に
相談しに行ったんだ
《（和）ずっと誰かに
見られてる気がする？→》
You've been feeling like someone's watching you?
I wonder if there's a stalker.
《ストーカーのたぐいかしら》
It's hard to believe there's a stranger on campus, but...
《学内に不審者がいるとは
考えにくいけど…》
《うん？　何　泣いてんのよ》
Why are you crying?
《普通の反応してもらえたのが
嬉しくて…》
I'm just so happy that I got a normal response.
《〈（和）軽音部で
どんな扱い受けてるの…〉》
How do they treat you at the Light Music Club?
《・（曽我部）真鍋さん　いるかしら》
Manabe-san, are you in?
Senpai.
《先輩》
《（曽我部）あら　お客さん？》
Oh my, a guest?
Is something wrong?
《・（曽我部）引き継ぎの資料
持ってきたんだけど》
I brought the documents.
Nodoka, who's she?
《和　この人は？》
She's our current president, Sokabe Megumi-san.
《・（和）生徒会長の
曽我部　恵さんよ》
《（曽我部）「元」　だけどね
よろしく　秋山さん》
Ex-president.
Nice to meet you, Akiyama-san.
《あ…　はい》
《やっぱり軽音部の人は》
Oh, sure.
I figured people from the Light Music Club wouldn't know me...
《私のこと　知らないか～》
《あああッ　す　すいませんッ》
I'm so sorry!
That was how they fatefully met!
〈それが
２人の出会いだった〉
But then, Mio knew not about the destiny that awaited her.
〈だが　この後に
待ち受ける運命のことなど〉
〈このときの澪は
知るよしもなかった〉
Cut out the creepy narration.
勝手に
変なナレーション入れるなッ
それって
どんな運命だったんですか
What sort of destiny was it?
どんなもこんなも…
Well, if you must know...
Here you go.
《（曽我部）どうぞ　軽音部みたいに
いいお茶じゃないけど》
Though it's not as good as the tea you have at your club.
Oh, no. This is perfectly fine.
《そんな　おかまいなく》
In any case, it's quite serious if there's really a stalker.
《それにしてもストーカーなんて
ゆゆしき問題ね→》
Manabe-san, can you inform the
disciplinary committee about this?
《真鍋さん　後で風紀委員に
この件伝えてもらえる？》
《（和）わかりました》
《あ　あのッ》
Very well.
U-Umm, you don't have to do so much.
《そこまで　してもらわなくても…》
《いいのよ　うちの学校の
生徒が困ってるんだから》
Don't worry.
We just want to be of help when a fellow student is in trouble.
《何か力になりたいの》
《〈（澪）うちの部長に
聞かせたいなあ…〉》
If only our club president could hear that...
But what kind of person would be after Mio?
《（和）だけど
澪を追いかけ回す人って》
《どんな人かしら》
《（曽我部）ファンクラブの人…　とか？》
Someone in her fanclub, maybe?
No. Not that...
《ううッ　そのことは…》
《あら　どうかした？》
Oh, is something wrong?
No...
《いいえ　会長は軽音部のこと
いろいろ　お詳しいんですね》
I'm amazed you know so much about our club.
《私の名前も知ってたし》
《えッ》
You even knew my name.
《・（和）そういえば　軽音部で
お茶会してることも→》
Oh yeah, you also knew they have tea at their club.
《知ってたんですね》
《えと…　ま　真鍋さんが前に
教えてくれたんじゃない》
Well...
You told me, didn't you Manabe-san?
《私　言ってないですよ》
《そうだったかしら》
I don't remember doing so.
Really?
But the Light Music Club is
pretty famous in many ways.
《でも　軽音部って
いろんな意味で有名だしね→》
《それじゃあ
そろそろ私　行くわね》
I need to be going now.
《（和）先輩　何か落としましたよ》
Senpai, you dropped something.
《（和）「秋山澪
ファンクラブ会員証」…》
Akiyama Mio Fanclub membership card.
I... found it in the hall.
《（曽我部）さっき
廊下で拾ったのよ》
But isn't that your name on the card?
《でも　先輩の名前
書いてありましたけど…》
I have to say something to break up this awkwardness.
《〈（澪）ここは私が何か言って
場を落ち着かせなきゃ！〉》
Could you possibly be the culprit?
《〈会長が犯人だったりして～〉》
《〈何でやね～ん！〉》
Why would I be?
《〈（澪）よし　これでいこう〉》
A flawless plan!
C-Could you possibly be the stalker?
《じ　実は　会長がストーカーの
犯人だったりして～》
I wasn't trying to scare you!
《（曽我部）悪気はなかったのッ》
《（澪・和）ええ～ッ！！》
《・（曽我部）もうすぐ私
卒業でしょ？→》
I'm almost graduating...
《今みたいに　秋山さんに会えなく
なっちゃうって思ったら→》
So I was thinking about how I won't see you anymore, and...
《いてもたっても
いられなくなって…》
I just couldn't hold myself back...
Don't worry about it.
《（澪）いいんです》
《えッ》
It feels nice to hear someone say so much about me.
《そこまで
言ってもらえて私も嬉しいですし》
《恥ずかしいですけど…》
Though it's a bit embarrassing.
Akiyama-san...
《秋山さん…》
Member 001?
《（和）会員ナンバー１番…》
Oh, I'm also the president of the fanclub.
《あッ　私
ファンクラブの会長でもあるの》
《ええ～ッ》
それじゃあ
生徒会長が犯人だったんですか？
So the student council president was the stalker?
立場上　それは
言いづらいわよね
No wonder she couldn't be open about it.
Yeah...
ええ　まあ…
So we wanted to do something for Sokabe-senpai.
だから私達
そんな曽我部先輩のために
何か
できないかな～って思ったんだ
そう　それで…
Yeah.
And...
The Light Music Club asked us to come here, but I wonder what they're planning...
《（和）軽音部に講堂に来るように
言われましたけど　何でしょうね》
Are they trying to get me back?
《（曽我部）お礼参りとか…》
《（和）まさかそんな…》
No, they wouldn't-
《曽我部先輩　ご卒業…》
Sokabe-senpai, congratulations on your graduation.
《（全員）おめでとうございます！》
《あの…　私達　桜高軽音部が
お祝いの意味を込めて→》
Umm...
We, the Sakura High Light Music Club, would like to congratulate you with a performance.
《演奏させていただきます→》
Please enjoy.
《聴いてください》
《（全員）「ふわふわタイム」》
Light and Fluffy Time!
《ワン　ツー
ワン　ツー　スリー　フォー》
One, two...
One, two, three, four!
《・～》
Senpai?
《・（和）先輩　先輩ッ》
Senpai!
《演奏終わってますよ》
《ハッ！》
They're done.
《無断で講堂を使用するなんて！》
《（澪）えッ》
Who said you could use the auditorium?!
Is what I would say as president.
《というのは建て前で》
Thank you, everyone.
《ありがとう　みんな
こんな贈り物　初めてよ》
It's the first time I've gotten anything like this.
《あ…　笑った～！》
She smiled!
As a memento...
《・（曽我部）記念に…→》
Can I have your autograph?
《サインくださいッ
「みおたんより」って書いて！》
And add "from Mio-tan"?
《〈（和）そうめいな
先輩のイメージが…〉》
My intellectual image of her is crumbling...
書いたんですか？　みおたん…
And you really wrote it?
（澪）書いた…
先輩　とっても喜んでたわ
I did...
She was overjoyed.
The first membership card?
（梓）会員番号１番の会員証！？
しかも　和の名前？
And your name's on it?!
Well, later that day...
（和）実は　あの後…
Well then, Manabe-san.
《それじゃ
ファンクラブ会長の方も》
I'd like you to take after my role as the fanclub president as well.
《引き継ぎよろしくね！》
《（和）い・り・ま・せ・んッ》
I do not want it!
Well...
（和）この会員証　断り切れなくて
受け取ったんだけど→
I couldn't turn her down completely, so I accepted it,
結局　機会がなくて　会長としての
責務を何一つ果たせなかった
but I haven't had any chance to do
anything president-like for the club since.
和ちゃん…
（和）だから　今日はお願いに来たの
Nodoka-chan...
So I came to ask you all a favor today.
ファンクラブの子達のために
お茶会を開いてもらえないかな
Can you host a tea party for all the fanclub members?
A tea party?
・（紬）お茶会？
・（和）そう
Yeah.
このままじゃ
先輩にも申し訳なくて…
If I don't do something, I'd feel really bad for Senpai.
Okay!
わかった　私達も協力するよッ
（澪）えッ？
We'll help!
It's the least we can do for
someone who helps us all the time!
いつも　和には
助けてもらってるからなッ
ええッ
どんなお茶会にする？
Now, the question is what sort of tea party?
ムギまで！？　あの　落ち着いて…
ケーキカットは外せないし～
Mugi, you too?
Guys, calm down.
Let's see what we need...
We definitely need to cut cake like a wedding!
花束贈呈と　思い出のアルバムとか
披露宴！？
And a bouquet! A memorial album too!
Whose wedding?!
Then how about a Q&A session too?
・（梓）質問コーナー　どうですか
それ　いいね～！
Nice idea!
〈（澪）聞いてない…〉
They're in their own world...
それじゃあ　お言葉に甘えて
お茶会の中身の方は
Then is it all right if I leave the whole tea party in your hands?
みんなに任せていいかしら
私は　会場を押さえたり
I'll look for a place to hold the
party and also spread the word.
告知をしたりするわ
I'll make posters.
私　ポスター作ってきます
（紬）特大のケーキ持ってきます！
I'll bring a giant cake.
Mugi, you're way too into this!
ムギ　ノリすぎ！
いいじゃん
Come on, we don't get to do this every day.
With everyone's help, I think this will be an amazing tea party, Sokabe-senpai.
〈（和）素敵なお茶会に
なりそうです　曽我部先輩〉
・（和）だんだん
本格的になってきたわね
It looks like the preparations are going smoothly.
It'll all be about Mio-chan for all her fans!
澪ちゃんファンのために
大盤ぶるまい
澪ちゃん鉛筆　澪ちゃん消しゴム
澪ちゃんティッシュ
Mio-chan pencil, Mio-chan eraser, Mio-chan tissue,
Mio-chan chocolate, Mio-chan can opener, Mio-chan chopsticks,
澪ちゃんチョコ
澪ちゃん栓抜き　澪ちゃんお箸に
and Mio-chan backscratcher.
澪ちゃん孫の手　と
These things are all creepy!
（澪）変なものまで作るなッ
I just put your sticker on it.
澪ちゃんシール貼っただけ
It's simple but cute, don't you think?
お手軽だけど　かわいいでしょう？
（澪）もらってうれしいのか？　それ
Would someone even want something like that?
憂がクッキーも焼いてくれたわ
澪ちゃんクッキーですよ！
Ui also baked cookies.
Mio-chan cookies!
（澪）ハア…
律先輩
Ritsu-senpai, I hope you're not
thinking about charging anyone.
「会費は？」　なんて
言いださないでくださいよ
何を～　人を守銭奴のように！
Don't treat me like some golddigger!
（ノック）
は～い！
失礼します
Yes?
Excuse me.
We brought some food.
差し入れを持ってきました
ホントに！？
Really?
We'd like you all to have it.
皆さんで食べてください
どうぞ
ありがとう～
Here.
Thank you.
あッ　焼きそばパンだよ
お茶まであるッ
It's yakisoba bread!
And tea!
Can we have some right now?
食べていい？
・（梓）手　はやッ
You're so quick.
あ…　ありがとう
Thank you.
We're looking forward to the tea party.
お茶会　楽しみにしてますッ
失礼しました！
Excuse us.
ありがとね～
かわいい～
Thanks a lot.
They're so cute.
みんな　楽しみに
してくれてるみたいで　よかった
I'm glad they're all excited about it.
それで　肝心の
曽我部先輩は来るのか？
So, is Sokabe-senpai even coming?
それが…
Well...
・（梓）え～ッ　来れない？
She can't make it?
I wrote her a letter, but she said she can't
come because she has club activities that day.
手紙は書いたんだけど　その日は
サークルの旅行で来られないって
Then what's the point of this party?
それじゃあ　意味ないですね…
Should we change the date?
日程　ずらす？
She also said we shouldn't change the date if we've already told everyone.
告知したんだったら　わざわざ
日程まで変える必要はないって
But that's...
そんな…
（和）曽我部先輩の望みは→
Sokabe-senpai said that she wishes for the continuation of the fanclub,
ファンクラブを継続させて
盛り上げることだからって→
and that it's enough to know the current members will have fun at the tea party.
お茶会で　ファンクラブの
現役会員達が楽しんでくれれば→
それで満足だからって
She sounds so mature.
何か　大人な発言…
女子大生だもんね
She's in college, after all.
卒業して　大人になって
澪ファンも卒業したってことか…
So she's become an adult after graduating,
and she's also graduated from being Mio's fan.
そんなことないですッ
きっとたまたま→
That can't be true!
I'm sure her hands are just full with other plans.
予定が重なって
仕方なかったんですよ
・（和）うん　私達に気を使わせない
ようにって思っただけなのかもね
Yeah.
She probably doesn't want us to be too considerate of her.
Sign: To Mio-senpai
I...
〈（澪）私も…　私も卒業したら→〉
I too wonder if I'm going to grow up like that once I graduate.
〈そんなふうに
大人に　なっちゃうのかな…〉
And Mio's heart was full with all the
glorious days she spent with her friends.
そのとき　澪の心には
友人達と過ごした幸せな日々が
走馬灯のように　ぐるぐるぐる…
（澪）勝手なナレーション　入れるなッ
I told you to stop narrating my life!
それじゃあ
日程もプログラムどおり
So let's continue according to original plans, without a change of date.
変更は
なしってことで進めましょう
Here, this is the program for the tea party.
（紬）はい　当日の進行表
I'd like Ricchan and Yui-chan to be the hosts.
司会は　りっちゃんと
唯ちゃんで　お願いします
Okay!
（律・唯）ウィ～ッ！
I'm thinking about decorating the music club for the party...
It's not on the program,
〈（澪）プログラムには
ないけど　私も→〉
〈みんなのために
何かやろうかな…〉
but maybe I'll do something for the fans too.
・（和）簡単で
お手軽なもので　やりましょう
I think something simple will do, without being too flashy.
So let's go over the program right now.
おいし…
It's good.
Well, thank you all for coming to the first Akiyama Mio Fanclub Tea Party today.
え～　本日は　第１回
秋山澪ファンクラブお茶会に
お集まりいただき
誠にありがとうございます
せん越ながら　司会を
務めさせていただきます
We are your hosts, Tainaka Ritsu, and...
私　田井中　律と
平沢　唯で～す
Hirasawa Yui!
Nice to meet you.
よろしくお願いしま～す！
There are a lot of people.
たくさん集まりましたね
何か　知ってる顔も　ちらほら…→
And I recognize quite a few faces...
えッ　佐々木さんも会員だったの？
Sasaki-san's also a member?
Yeah, it'll suddenly appear after the bumps in life!
人生には上り坂　下り坂
そして突然やってくる～
Ricchan, that also applies to weddings!
りっちゃん　それも結婚式！
Well, enough of the comedy act, and let's get this tea party started.
ショートコントはこの辺にして
秋山澪ファンクラブお茶会の開催です
Enter, the star of the party...
本日の主役の入場！
秋山み～お～！
Akiyama Mio!
（拍手と歓声）
Mio-chan's so cool!
澪ちゃん　かっこいい！
でも　制服つまんな～い
But why's she wearing that boring uniform?
Don't worry, we'll take care of that.
大丈夫！　お色直しがありますッ
No, you won't!
いや　ないからッ
（唯・律・さわ子）ええ～ッ　ブ～ブ～
本日はお忙しい中　おあつめ…
Thank you all for coming despit-
・（会員Ａ）かんだ！
・（Ｂ）でもそこがまた…
She bit her tongue!
But that's what makes her so...
・（Ｃ）かわいい～！
ウケてる…
So cute!
They love it.
おおお　お集まりいた　いたがき…
Coming despite your-
Despite your... jizzy...
板垣…　退助？
私達のコントよりウケてるよ
マジでか…
They like it more than our introduction.
Are you serious?
それでは
スピーチはこの辺にして
Now that her speech is done, let's have cake.
ケーキ入刀に移ります！
さあ　澪ちゃんどうぞ！
初めての共同作業です
Okay Mio-chan, go ahead.
Your first shared event!
With whom?!
誰との！？
あずにゃんが　お手伝いします
Azu-nyan will help you.
ええ～ッ
We are now offering cake and tea service,
それでは　これより
ケーキとお茶のサービス
as well as Akiyama Mio's candle service.
および　秋山澪本人による
キャンドルサービスを行いま～す
Senpai, I need you over here next.
先輩！　次　こっちお願いします！
（澪）えッ？
This table too.
こっちも！
ひいッ
I would like to now move on to the special event.
それでは　特別企画に
移りたいと思います
In other words, 100 questions for Akiyama Mio!
題して　秋山澪への
１００の質問コーナー！
ちなみに　質問に一つ答えるたび
テーブルのキャンドルを
By the way, please put out one candle on your table for each question she answers.
一つずつ
消していってく～ださい
Now, let's go with the first question.
まず最初の質問　これまで
聞いた中で一番怖かった話は？
What's the scariest story you've heard in your life?
Why are you asking me something like that?
えッ　何てこと聞くんだッ
次の質問！
Now the next question: what was the second scariest story?
２番目に怖かった話は？
ひいいい～ッ
And the next one: what was the third?
次の次の質問
３番目に怖かった話は～？
やめろ～ッ！
次の次の次の質問！
Stop!
Okay, let's go with the next one.
What was the fourth scariest story?!
百物語？
One Hundred Thriller Tales?
Stop!
Next question!
Stay strong.
（Ｄ）頑張って～
（Ｅ）ファイトです～
You're so beautiful.
Mio-san...
では皆さんも
質問したい人～
Now, your turn!
Who has a question?
I do! I do!
Me!
Where do you wash first when you take a bath?
（Ｆ）お風呂に入ったら
どこから洗いますか？
シャ　シャワーヘッド？
風呂掃除！？
The shower head.
You clean the bath?
Do you eat taiyaki from the head?
（Ｇ）たい焼きは
頭から食べる派？
エラぶた？
どこ～！？
The gill cover.
Where?!
Now, let's move on to the next event on the program.
それでは　次のプログラムに
移りたいと思いま～す
I'd like for us to reflect on the first half of
Mio-chan's life with the following slideshow.
今　こうやって立派に
育った澪ちゃんの半生を
スライド写真とともに
振り返りたいと思います！
I'll only live to see 34?
〈（澪）１７歳で　もう半分…？〉
（Ｈ）めちゃくちゃかわいい…
（佐々木）大きく育ったのね…
She's so tiny and cute.
She's grown so big.
She's too cute.
（Ｉ）かわいすぎる…
Why does it look more like Ritsu-senpai's slideshow?
何か　澪先輩より
律先輩の方が目立ってません？
うちのアルバムから
持ってきた写真だからなッ
Well, these pictures are from my album collection.
いよいよ　お茶会も
終わりに近づいてまいりました
The tea party is nearing its end.
それでは　フィナーレは私達
放課後ティータイムの演奏で…
We'd like to end this party with a performance from us, the Afterschool Tea Time-
・（澪）ちょっと待ってッ
Wait.
Umm...
あのッ　皆さんに
聞いてほしいものが　あります→
I have something I'd like for you all to hear.
I don't think I'm good at using prose to convey my feelings,
私　口じゃうまく　この気持ちを
伝えられそうにないから…→
詩を作ってきました
so I wrote a poem.
おおッ　サプライズ！
A surprise!
Glittereth the sugar,
「ときめきシュガー」→
「大切なあなたに
カラメルソース」→
An ingredient for the caramel sauce I mix for you.
「グラニュー糖に
ブラウンシュガー」
Granulated sugar, brown sugar,
「メープル　ハチミツ　和三盆」→
Maple, honey, wasanbon sugar,
「あなたのために　カラメルソース」
All ingredients for the caramel sauce I mix for you.
My heart is also like caramel sauce.
「私のハートも　カラメルソース」
A little burn matters not, for you help make this sauce taste better!
「ちょっぴり焦げついちゃっても」
「あなたの
火加減で　おいしくなるの！」
あッ　あ…
さすがにファンでも　澪の
境地には　たどり着けなかったか
Her fans couldn't follow her at all.
（律・唯）それでは
ここで演奏で～す
Now, let's have a performance.
It'll feature our latest song,
放課後ティータイムの新曲
「ぴゅあぴゅあはーと」です！
Pure-Pure Heart!
Let's go! Let's go!
・～
My head is full of you.
・～頭の中　想いでいっぱい
In fact, I'm worried it'll overflow.
・～あふれそうなの　ちょっと心配
・～とりあえず
ヘッドホンで　ふさごう
I'll put on my headphones and sing this moment away for now.
・～Ｄｏｎ’ｔ　ｓｔｏｐ　ｔｈｅ　ｍｕｓｉｃ！
Don't stop the music.
I'm honest when I want something.
・～欲しいものは
欲しいって言うの
I'm honest when I want to do something.
・～したいことは
したいって言うの
・～だけど言えない言葉もあるの
But there are a few things I can't honestly say.
・～Ｃａｎ’ｔ　ｓｔｏｐ　ｔｈｅ　ｈｅａｒｔｂｅａｔ！
Can't stop my heartbeat.
Suddenly!
・～いきなり！　チャンス到来
A chance comes around; I didn't know he lived in my direction.
・～ぐうぜん同じ帰り道　Ｗｏｗ！
Inflation!
・～ふくらむ胸の風船
The balloon in my heart blows up and sweeps me off my feet.
・～急に足が宙に浮くの
・～上昇気流にのって
Now, ride the wind, and fly away!
・～飛んでいっちゃえ！
キミのもとへ
I hope you fly, my pure-pure heart, to where he is.
・～わたしの　ぴゅあぴゅあはーと
I'm not scared at all if he'll accept it.
・～受けとめてくれるなら
恐くはないの
・～この気持ちが
大気圏　越えたとき
When my feelings broke through the atmosphere,
・～キミは見えなくなってた
I couldn't see you anymore.
You were across of the street, but I don't mind.
・～道の向こう側
あい☆　Ｄｏｎ’ｔ　ｍｉｎｄ
Say cheese!
はい　チーズ！
Okay, eyes over here now.
次　こっち目線お願いしま～す
・（紬）次　こっち向いてくださ～い
And this way.
みんな澪に寄りすぎだって～
Girls, you're going to smush Mio.
この盛り上がり
曽我部先輩にも見せたかったな
I wish I could have shown this to Sokabe-senpai.
I know!
そうだッ
What are you going to do with a cellphone photo?
そんなの撮って　どうするの？
I'm going to send it to Sokabe-senpai.
送ってあげるんです
曽我部先輩に
えッ　でも　携帯のアドレス…
But do you know her number?
（梓）アドレスは
生徒会で調べてください！
That will be your job.
（サークル仲間）飲み物買ってくるね
（曽我部）うん
I'm going to go buy some drinks.
（メール着信）
うふッ　また
素敵な贈り物　もらっちゃった
They gave me another wonderful gift.
Dear Sokabe-senpai.
〈（和）拝啓　曽我部先輩→〉
By all means, please come next time.
〈今度は先輩も
ぜひ　いらしてください→〉
〈きっと
楽しいお茶会に　なりますよ〉
I think you will definitely have a great time.
・～
Deep, deep inside my heart,
there was a sanctuary where nothing ever resounded.
But now it's burning with heat, so I've forever changed.
I send out shockwaves to the world, as storms,
and tsunamis invite each other with the sound of rock and roll
to walk beside each other everywhere they go.
Whoops, I dropped my pick,
and I broke my drumstick, but hey it's all right.
I'm still a part of the usual sound,
which is actually quite miraculous!
We'll sing out loud to our hearts' content.
No matter how faint the song,
it's the one and only in the world.
We want to live our lives to the fullest
so that we won't care if we die today.
Let's play our passion to the world.
After all, this is our precious heartbeat.
We'll sing our treasured heartbeat.
So please listen!!
Preview
It's your future, so you should really take the time to think about it.
But I can't really think about something that won't happen for a while.
Yui, you still haven't turned in your plans for the future?
I know that feeling.
Is that how it is?
Well, I think you can just put down whatever naturally comes to you.
Something that naturally comes to me...
The Future!
I know!